Ending
(Ten billion points for the privilege I'll give it to you)
I have to answer I have to answer I have to answer
That was a lot of work on the way to the end.
♪
I'll put my ear to the ground.
I hate this fashion show.
Lan Yong's floor is a footbath.
Failure
[ED]
Oh no, oh no.
It's okay.
It's okay, guys. It's okay. We're gonna be okay.
It's going to be okay.
AKB48.
How was the holistic version?
Love from here.
Include NG. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Good morning.
I didn't maze.
I was working on the code section of the contraption.
It turned into a maze.
What? That's not good.
You're dizzy.
Yes, I am.
But we'll make it work.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Inari-san!
Mena's local "Inari".
Inari-san.
She never sleeps. Today she did.
The manager will get angry with her.The manager would get mad at me.
What time did you get up?
Like 6:00.
That's cute.
We have rehearsal at 12:30 for the night show,
I've got a beauty parlor.
I'll do my best for rehearsal.
Yay!
Where should I put this?
I forgot my VIVS.
I think this will be fine.
It would have been better without it.
Oh no.
We don't have time before the day of the show,
I don't even have time to rehearse now.
I'm a little nervous.
Saito, my name is Arisa. I'm Arisa Saito.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'd be happy if you could hit the sound when Misato Hayashi in the very back raises her voice.
Yes, understood.
Please do.
Yes, ma'am.
If you see the rehearsal, we're getting more aware of ourselves.
You know, checking our own triggers and all that.
I think we're getting the feeling that we're going to make this stage better and deliver it to the fans.
I think we are getting the feeling that we are going to make this stage better and deliver it to the fans.
Thank you for your hard work.
You come here every time, don't you?
Thank you very much.
He says he doesn't like it twice.
You call him cute?
Tell him he's cute.
What if she says I'm cute?
That would be great.
It's great to be called cute.It's amazing to be told I'm pretty.
That's amazing.
Miri dressed me.
You can dress me? That's amazing.
Yes, I can.
It was a simple kaita.
Good luck.
Thank you very much.
I changed my clothes. It's a change.
Are you wearing a yukata today?
That's right. I'm wearing a yukata.
For the daytime performance.
I wonder how much they will dance.
It might be too much.
Unexpectedly.
I might fly in as a surprise.
Please catch me.
Bye-bye.
I've never done this kind of MCing before, but I have to, so I'll do my best,
But I have to do it, so I'll do my best.
I'm anxious, but I'll do my best.
I'm anxious about the catch.
I'm really here now.
I will do my best. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
The real one is Saki Natsume.
Then I hope I will be able to go from the customer's outro.
We are waiting for you.
I'll be waiting for you.
Wow!
The seats are all the way in the back.
Isn't it amazing? It's pretty full!
Everyone's wearing T-shirts!
Oh, green, red, orange...Oh, green, red, orange.
I bet you're wearing a T-shirt by the Nakagawa family.
This one's okay too, right?
Uh, it's Mom and Dad.
That's a good one.
Nice dad, nice mom.
Seino!
Negumina! Negumina! 100% with all of you!
Full expression
Passion
Smile
Growth
Confidence
Gratitude
charm
Us
LoveLoveBoo!
Hello!
Hello everyone!
They're singing for us.
Okay, well, I'd like to get right to the next project, the special project.
I always answer the big question that you guys love to think about, please give me time to think.
You even process them, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Oh, no.
Oh, no!
Don't look back.
That was delicious.
That was good.
I'm overflowing with what you just said.
Not at all.
I'm sure there are people here.
You told me it was okay to cry.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You're number one.
Please.
I'm afraid I don't have time to do it in full.
Do you have a particular area you'd like to work on?
I don't have a number one.
I'm off.
There's a lot of pressure to do comedy in the time we have to think about it.
And Arisa put a comedy in her comedy act, so...
I'm scared.
Oh no!
And I haven't eaten lunch yet.
I haven't eaten breakfast either.
Not even breakfast? You only ate your neck?
If we work hard today...
All right, let's do it.
Okay, here are the totals.
Oh, shit.
The last one was after the turnaround.
When it's over.
I was hoping you'd make up your mind.
Bamboo shooter.
That's enough!
You think you can just say "bamboo copter" and be done with it
You don't have the guts.
Let's eat.
If you're going to eat it...
I don't want to get hit.
What's in it for you?
I can't believe I'm going to be this overjoyed.
Wait, wait, wait.
In time to think
When I told him about the rabbit and the summit
My knees are tight
I thought it was the worstI thought it was the most dangerous.
Come on.
It's okay. It's okay.
Hang in there, guys.
It's going to be okay.
Why did Saito say that?
Bold!
I don't want to do it.
Yes, we'll do it.
Thank you for watching.
It's the day of Summer's second one-man show.
A tiff, three new songs, and a second show.
That's a crazy busy schedule.
I think they're doing a great job.
It's a big place for a second one-man show.
It's not my decision. I'm shocked.
I thought you'd take it a little slower. I thought so.
But I want you to get through this one last time.
Once we get through this, and then the last six months...
I'm going to take the last six months or so and switch it up.
I'd like to think about these kids, or rather the riffraff, too.
I'll just have to do my best.
Thanks for watching:)
Sakuma, may I have a word with you, since it was a long time ago?
Please do.
I mean a long time ago. I'm amazed that you have come this far even though you have only debuted about half a year ago.
I really think my strength is your efforts.
But it's still not enough.
So please work hard, one by one, to break your own personal best record and show us your charm.
I'll do my best.
Please do your best.
Yes, I will. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
Make it last!
Make it last! Make it last! Everybody first, 100 points!Make it last! Make it last! 100 points for everyone first!
All over! Impression! Passion! Smile! All your energy! Sentiment! See us! We!
Rock, paper, scissors! Rock, paper, scissors!
Icole shot!
Gentlemen, can you play rock-paper-scissors?
Moth Horn
Cast a spell on this life with my song and dance
Cast a spell on this life with your voice, come on
Tiger, lion, sliver, fiber, diver, viper
Jawline, jawline, 2ID
Heart, life, will, outman, heart, curve, smash
Negimera, gripe, gripe, gripe, gripe, gripe, gripe, gripe, gripe
If someone was crying, I wouldn't leave them behind.
Raspberry Sinner
Natsu nakan anxious kohotai katsu renzome
Ruff Ruff is a great comedy!
Give me time to think!
I have to tell you, I have to answer you
What is the title of the third live show that everyone was against?
I have to tell, I have to answer
No. 1 Airi Saito
If I lose to Bakarhythm in a comedy contest, I'll have to go straight to the breakup live!
Ha-ha-ha!
I can't believe my ears when I hear the words I just shook off.
I don't care if it's a lie, just make the audience excited!
No.4 Yui Takanashi
After today, Sakuma-san will win 10 billion point dance here!
Yay!
Please give a big mouth to the fans!
No. 9 Yui Fujisaki
Within a year, we'll have a ground progress program!
Oh!
I want it to happen! I want it to happen! I want to make it happen!
Let's go for it!
Thank you so much.Thank you very much.
Three minutes will elapse shortly.
I need a drink of water.
Do you have time for a drink?
Your time will be up shortly.
Thank you very much.
Are you guys willing to do this?
You don't have enough guts.
You're all going to hell!
It's hard to find someone who goes to heaven with a dentist resurrection.
All you have to do is make me laugh.
Here are the materials for this afternoon.
There are 6 participants.
Let's see...
I wonder if any of them are funny.
What the hell is this place?
This place?
It's a system where all the dead idols come here.
It's called "Dentist Resurrection Hell Auditions".
All idols can go to hell.
But if you make Enma laugh, you can go to heaven.
My name is Takanashi Yui, number 50.
I want to go to heaven.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
What's this guy's scene? Takanashi's scene is about encountering hot and spicy food she can't eat, and she's shocked.
Heppoko pappageuse!
The material says that his favorite food is very spicy... So, the subject is, "What is the surprising way to eat spicy food without it being spicy?
Thinking time is about to start!
[ED]
Thinking time is over.
What is the surprising way to eat hot and spicy food without it being spicy?
It's small and its member's color is orange.
The legendary idol who is small, whose member color is orange, and whose habit is to talk in tones, is going to perform a secret technique to make her sweet.
No, I don't know this idol.
I'm not interested in that idol.
But it was very funny, wasn't it?But it was really funny.
Stop with the family data.
Next.
51st Chief, Matsusharu.
I want to go to heaven.
I look forward to working with you.
According to his file...
"My favorite food is dinosaurs.
So, what's your subject?
There's a noise at night at the dinosaur museum.
Why?
Cut me loose.
Because they make me cut off so much.
Triceratops and Tyrannosaurus.
"Uh-uh-uh-uh," they arm-wrestle.
"Uh-uh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
How do dinosaurs arm-wrestle?
Kesketh.
Dinosaurs have short front legs.
That's what a big slash is.
It's a reverse slash.
Reverse slash!
Sacrana to Emma!
He's going to hell.
Let's do a hundred different boxes, you prick.
Inflate a lot of balloons, a lot of balloons
Two ways to say "Oh" or "Ouch"!
It's so delicious!
If you're wondering why it's so good, it's so good!
For an extra 2,000 yen, you can have a mena good boy good boy ow!
Come here, Emma!
You know you lost in the second round of the Japan Broadcasting Corp.
Don't talk about comedy.
Lady Emma.Lady Emma.
Remember me, Kes!
Farewell, Yaas!
It would be nice if we could have a reborn group with these members someday.
It would be nice to have a stronger bond with everyone!
This was the beginning of ruff ruff.
Thanks for all your hard work.
Answer.
Chapchera!
That's it now.
Don't need to know Don't need to understand
I don't want to squeeze it in too deep. That's still good enough for now.
We are Dunkaroo!
We're so happy right now.
Where is it? Where is it?
Come on, Millikids!
Wrong head.
Seaworth.
I've had a tough time, but I'll never forget the view from my first debut live,
The more I stand on stage, the more I want to go to bigger and bigger places, and that's why I've been an idol ever since.
Seeing your faces today made me feel glad that I have worked so hard until now,
I hope that we can become a group that can continue to grow together with the 9 members and the fan group.
I hope that we can grow together with the 9 members and the fan group.
I had another audition last year and my dream that didn't come true was to be on the TIFF Smile Guide,
It came true this summer, so I would like to aim for a bigger dream next time.
Some of the guests came to the festival for the first time today,
I think we are here because of the summer festivals that we have attended so far.
I would like to give a performance that can deliver more to the fans...
I would like to give a performance that can reach out to our fans even more.
I will do my best to make the current members of the Lafree Corps like us even more,
I will do my best to make the new members of the Lafree Corps like us even more.
I'll do my best to make the new Lafree Corps members like me as well,
I hope that everyone will be able to see it,
I'm sure that everyone can see that you have made a mistake, or that you have made a mistake in position,
Even when they make mistakes that are obvious to everyone,
They are so warm and smile at you,The warmth and laughter,
It was very reassuring.
I also enjoy myself,
I want to make my customers smile,
I want to make them happy.
The other day, I asked all the members to read the letters they had written to their past and future selves.
I am sure that the past me was afraid to realize that I wanted to be an idol.
But thanks to you, Sakura, for getting back on your feet to take the P idol audition.
Thanks to you, I am living my dream.
I still don't have confidence at all, but I can be proud of myself now!
During the summer vacation, all my classmates quit the club.
I found an audition and passed it, and now I'm an idol!
Life is what it's meant to be, so do what you want to do!
I'll take care of the rest.
I'm 17 years old, and I want to say one thing to you.
I'm 17 years old and all I want to say is to take care of the people around you.
I used to be so cocky.
I'd say, "I take good care of them".
Then take better care of yourself
Don't give up on your dream, no matter what.
You're in such a great place
In the past, I wasn't aiming for anything.
I just loved idols.
That's when I saw this
Nobuyuki Sakuma's idol production project
Now I'm in such a wonderful place with people I love
I'm able to live so that today is more enjoyable than yesterday.
To the old Yusa Saito
I was a nervous psychologist, unsure about everything, a crybaby, and couldn't show myself much.
I was in trouble many times, wasn't I?
I always tried to overcome my problems through trial and error.
I tried all kinds of things and somehow managed to do my best.
That's why I want to tell my old self to never stop trying.
I want you to believe in your future self and keep going.
To my future self
How are you doing?How are you doing?
Even if you're making mistakes and messing up...
You should be proud of what you have done so far!
Keep up the fight with the courage and energy you had when you DMed Sakuma
Please continue to fight with your energy in your heart.
Are you living with pride?
Are you still scared of meeting your old classmates in your hometown
Are you still scared of your old classmates?
I wish I could get used to it so that I don't have to be!
As long as I'm enjoying my life, that's all that matters to me.
To my future self, late 20s
How old do you want to continue being an idol?
I want them to continue until they are satisfied with themselves.
I also want her to get a driver's license.
Anyway, if you have any doubts...
Think back to the time when you were dreaming of becoming an idol
Compared to the time when you were wondering how you could become an idol
Now that you are an idol, it's a luxury to have worries.
Please continue to do your best in your own way, and don't take advantage of the environment.
Based on their message
A song was completed based on their message.
Do you remember me from that day?
I can only say this now
The dream I've been longing for will continue
Hey, I'm drawing a picture
Don't worry if you cry
I'm smiling in the future
Someday
In this wonderful place
Then and now
Will be connected
Always
Let's go straight ahead
Proud of the future and us
Believe in the future, Be myself
Future meMe in the future
How are you?
Are you living with your heart in your chest?
For all of this that's important to me.
Thank you and don't forget me
Be yourself
The future is a place of big dreams
Make dreams come true that cannot come true alone
Be myself
Let's live with a sparkling smile
Hold the unforgettable days in both hands
Always with a smile and all my strength
A good person you can count on
Be yourself
Just have fun
Make someone happy
Make all my dreams come true
I want to see a beautiful view
I want to make everyone smile
To the people of that day and to the people of the future
Be myself Someday, in this wonderful place
I'll hold in my heart the feelings I had back then
Be myself I'll always go straight ahead
Be myself
Everyone's going home.
What is it?
I'm going home.
I wrote letters to everyone.
Yay!
What?
Well, you all gave me that certificate from the first one-man show, so I thought it would be nice to return the favor.
I took the liberty of planning this.
That's selfish.
Thank you.
I've been writing to each of you individually, but today... well, let me read it to you.I've been writing to each of you individually, but today I'd like to read a little bit to all of you.
I wanted to write a letter to the members in return for the first one-man show.
It's been about a year since I auditioned for Ruff Ruff, and I can't believe how close we've become.
I never thought that we could become such good friends and become a group where we can support each other.
I'm really happy that we have become such good friends and a group that can support each other.
I really love each and every one of you!
Thank you for everything. The end.
You're crying so hard, Yuki-chan.
You have no choice but to call that guy.
That's a lie!
He was on Matsumoto Nakai.
Comedy Expectations
Nobuyuki Sakuma.
No way!
No, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
What?
You guys are crying too much.
You guys are crying so hard, you can't hold on to the chou chou, so you have to stop calling me.
No, really.
It's getting a little unbearable.
You know what?
It's really like this.
Second show, and more.
Thank you so much for coming to our last show at the Binoqua bread place.
Thank you very much.
If you came to our first show, you'll understand...
I don't say it to your face.
So I'm going to say this in the audience's direction.
My performance ability has improved a lot.
And more than anything
I'm glad to say that we've become good friends.
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes...
Yes, well...
I can't wait to see you too.I can't wait to be there.
I want to dance 10 billion point dance at Budokan
I want to dance 10 billion points at Budokan
Well, to be honest...
I've received 4 or 5 offers to dance 10 billion points on TV.
I've had 4 or 5 offers on TV, but I've turned them all down.
What!
That was with you guys.
It's to dance with you guys at the Budokan.
Yeah!
So you guys, I mean you guys.
I'm begging you all to take me to the Budokan.
You all take me to the Budokan!
Yeah!
Please take me to the Budokan!
Your ambiguous attitude
Don't tell me you don't care
Keep believing in yourself.
I have to say this.
I don't know.
I miss you.
All the time.
Pick your favorite color.
You know how I feel about you.
Come on, smile more.
Smile.
More, more, more.
Thank you for everything.
I love you guys.
More, more, more.
More and more and more.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for seeing me to the end!Thanks for watching to the end!
I'll be conversing with you today on the link!
Best regards!